https://scanpancookware.com/privacy/

0
To help us achieve our goal of providing the highest quality products and services, we use information from our interactions with you and other customers, as well as from other parties. Because we respect your privacy, we have procedures to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe, secure, and responsible manner.We have posted this privacy policy to let you know what kind of information we collect, how it is handled, with whom it may be shared, what choices you have regarding our use of your information, and how you may access some of the information you provide. Visit this page frequently for the most up-to-date information.
The information we collect
Whenever you shop with us we obtain from you the information we need to complete your transaction. This may include your name, address, telephone number, driver’s license number, birth date, and e-mail address. If you use a credit or debit card or pay by check, it will include your account number.
When you register with us as an online customer, we may ask for additional information, such as your favorite products.
If you use one of our services, or participate in one of our promotions or sweepstakes, we may ask for additional information, such as your age, interests or product preferences.
From your purchases and other interactions with us, we obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use.
To improve our Web site, we collect non-personal information about how users navigate through the site. This statistical information does not include individual names or personal data, so it does not identify you or any other customer.
We DO NOT share this information with anyone.
How we use the information we collect
We use the information we collect for various purposes, including:
to complete your purchase transactions
to provide the services you request
to send you our catalogs and other offerings by mail
to keep you informed about the status of your orders
to identify your product and service preferences, so we can notify you of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you
to notify you of product recalls or provide other information concerning products you have purchased
to improve our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall shopping experience A “cookie” is a small data file stored by your Web browser on your computer’s hard drive. It allows us to recognize your computer (but not specifically who is using it) upon entering our site by associating the identification numbers in the cookie with other customer information you have provided us. That customer information is stored on our secured database.
We use cookies to identify the pages you click on during your visit to our site and the name of the Web site you visited immediately before clicking to Scanpancookware.com. We use this information to improve our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions.
Accepting cookies through your Web browser is your personal choice.
Children’s privacy
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act took effect on April 21, 2000. It imposes certain requirements on Web sites directed at children under 13 that collect information on those children, and on Web sites that knowingly collect information on children under 13.
We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on our Web site, and our online sweepstakes are restricted to entrants who are at least 18 years old.
No one under the age of 15 should submit any personal information to this or any other Web site without the consent of a parent or guardian.
Specials
Classic
Professional
CTX
Classic Induction
Classic Knives
Gift Sets
Types
About
The WEB’s leading retailer of award winning Scanpan Cookware. Founded over 21 years ago, ScanpanCookware.com has built a loyal following of dedicated foodies who swear by the product. Scanpan is manufactured in Denmark to exacting standards that enable Scanpan to offer a conditional lifetime warranty for as long you own the product.
Facebook
Twitter
Previous
Next
Subscribe to our mailing list
* indicates required
Email Address
*
First Name
Last Name
Previous
Next
The WEB’s leading retailer of award winning Scanpan Cookware. Founded over 21 years ago, ScanpanCookware.com has built a loyal following of dedicated foodies who swear by the product. Scanpan is manufactured in Denmark to exacting standards that enable Scanpan to offer a conditional lifetime warranty for as long you own the product.
Facebook
Twitter
Subscribe to our mailing list
* indicates required
Email Address
*
First Name
Last Name
Free Knife Rack
Ordering this product will earn you a free magnetic knife rack.
Other Offers*
Free Scanpan Shears w/orders between $150 and $250
Free Rinse n Chop Cutting board w/orders between $250 and $450
Free Induction Cookplate with $690 of CTX Induction Cookware
*The highest value offer takes precedence. Only one offer is valid in any order. Our standard terms and conditions apply.This offer does not apply if the product is on clearance.
CLOSE
Free Rinse & Chop Strainer
Ordering this product will earn you a free rinse & chop cutting board/strainer.
Other Offers*
Free Scanpan shears w/orders between $150 and $250
Free Magnetic Rack with hooks($50 value) w/orders over $450
Free Induction Cookplate with $690 of CTX Induction Cookware
*The highest value offer takes precedence. Only one offer is valid in any order. Our standard terms and conditions apply.This offer does not apply if the product is on clearance.
CLOSE
Free Scanpan Kitchen Shears
Ordering this product will earn you a free pair of Scanpan Kitchen Shears.
Other Offers*
Free Rinse n Chop Cutting board w/orders between $250 and $450
Free Magnetic Rack with hooks($50 value) w/orders over $450
Free Induction Cookplate with $690 of CTX Induction Cookware
*The highest value offer takes precedence. Only one offer is valid in any order. Our standard terms and conditions apply. This offer does not apply if the product is on clearance.
CLOSE
We found this cheaper elsewhere and matched !!
We found this selling cheaper elsewhere and matched this price automatically.
The difference PLUS $1 will be deducted automatically when this product is added to your cart.
We continually scan competitors prices and automatically adjust where difference are found.
CLOSE
Free Induction Cooktop
Ordering $690 or more of CTX cookware will earn you a FREE Induction Cook Top*
Other Offers*
Free Scanpan Shears w/orders between $150 and $250
Free Rinse n Chop Cutting board w/orders between $250 and $450
Free knife rack w/orders between over $450
*The highest value offer takes precedence. Only one offer is valid in any order. Our standard terms and conditions apply
CLOSE
